Miss Re-l, why?
I didn't come here just to return that to you.
Tell me, Vincent Law.
Tell me about everything you know.
Miss Re-l...
I...
Don't lie.
Who would believe... something like that?
That you're...
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
Vince...
Is that scary lady going to come with us?
Who knows...
Would you be happy if she does, Vince?
You're making a funny face, Vince.
But...
You know, don't you?
You know that creature...
You know PROXY.
Why does it appear only when I'm around you?
How do you summon PROXY to you?
What are you?
I didn't know... for the longest time...
that I was a PROXY.
What are you-
I'm not summoning it to me!
I am PROXY.
She should go back to Romdeau.
meditation  when you're smiling
We've managed to catch up with the ship
without using the fuel we need to go back.
Hey! Scary lady!
This way, over here!
Hey!
That autoreiv's infected with cogito.
Iggy, wait in here.
But, Re-l!
What?
Um, I can't eat,
but I think it's so neat when I watch other people eat.
You make it hard for me to eat.
Get lost.
I'm sorry, Miss Re-l.
I won't believe it.
I won't believe that you're PROXY.
You might be right.
I know far less than what I don't know.
But... that's why I want to know.
Including myself, there are several
PROXIES remaining somewhere in this world.
Several?
How do you know for sure?
Because I feel it hasn't ended yet.
I have probably met two other PROXIES... and killed them.
What?
The first time, it was in Haros;
the second time, it was in Asura.
The PROXY I met the second time said...
that I have lost my memories.
My homeland, Mosk,
is directly involved in the loss of my memories.
If I go there, I should find something.
Now that I know I'm a PROXY,
I can't go back.
I see.
But you can't believe it, can you?
No.
Kill PROXY?
This is all that I can do for you right now.
This is the only way to kill the immortal PROXY.
These bullets are equipped with FP rays.
It's harmless to the human body,
but it affects the amrita cells only PROXY has.
No matter where it hits,
the FP rays will destroy the cells
and the PROXY should die - in theory.
I can't believe it.
Kill that monster...
However, this is only in theory.
So I'm entrusting these to you.
If you encounter PROXY by any chance...
Collect experimental data.
But Daedalus,
my primary objective is to capture PROXY.
It's my objective as well, of course.
I'll be waiting, Re-l.
Both Daedalus and I thought
that all the mysteries would be solved once we'd captured PROXY.
But is that true?
The lawless world I've been witness to...
What's anomalous
is that Romdeau alone can maintain order in such a world.
No...
Romdeau's crumbling as well.
The comatose PROXY went berserk and died.
The cogito virus is spreading.
There was a murder attempt on me,
the Representative's granddaughter.
Even if that man is PROXY,
just what could be gained by taking him back to Romdeau now?
I can't go on any further, either.
What should I do?
Re-l,
are you going to apprehend Vincent Law?
Either way, we have to go back to
Romdeau now, or we won't be able to at all.
You know that, right?
I don't believe it.
What?
But I must confirm it.
Re-l!
This man is PROXY...
If I shoot him, I can know for sure.
If he doesn't die, it's a lie.
But... if it's true...
No, impossible.
The FP bullet is harmless to humans.
I can just go for the legs.
Vincent Law...
I don't believe that you and PROXY are entirely unrelated.
That's why I came after you this far.
That might mean that I was drawn to you.
During my journey, I thought about you several times.
Are you PROXY?
Even so, I still must...
I love you.
What?
I love you, Miss Re-l.
But...
That an immigrant like me...
No, that's not it.
That a monster like me...
would think of you like that...
I thought I would never see you again.
I tried to let go many times.
But I still can't help loving you.
Who are you?!
Wait!
There are people here too?
How is it?
No good.
Even if we allow for the possibility that we can refuel somewhere,
it's too dangerous to go any farther.
The prince said it as well, didn't he?
That once we had only enough fuel for the return trip,
we were to return and report.
You have to consider the prince's concern for you.
Your cute boyfriend's feelings, that is.
Daedalus is my primary care physician.
In any case, let's return to Romdeau for now,
Re-l.
You're quite happy-go-lucky, aren't you, Iggy.
In Romdeau, Re-l Mayer is dead.
The prince will do something about that too.
My pride doesn't permit that.
If I go back now, it means I wasted my time.
But...
I know!
If our ship can't make the trip, we have that man's ship!
That ship moves by wind power.
It doesn't look sophisticated, but
we won't need to worry about fuel.
You're saying we should seize their ship?
Maybe.
Do you want to stay with that guy so much?
I wonder.
He seems to want me to, at least.
Huh?
He has feelings for me.
Besides,
I don't want to go back to Romdeau yet.
Re-l...
Are you finished yet?
Oh, yeah I'm done.
I'm going to resolve this.
Definitely.
Hey, Pino.
Gone...
Jeez.
I wish she'd learn a few things from Miss Re-l's Entourage.
You came to the rabbit yesterday, didn't you?
Since the rabbit broke down, Vince's been going, "Bang, bang"!
I ran away because of the all the noise.
Hey, why are you so quiet?
You don't want to talk with me?
You can't speak?
Vince...
What's going on?
Don't.
That autoreiv is infected.
Stay here.
It's too late to worry about that.
Vincent Law...
Lady!
Vincent... you...
Vince!
Vincen-
I'm sure he'll be fine.
Vince is strong!
Re-l!
Iggy...
Where are you going?
It's dangerous.
Lady!
Re-l!
Vincent has...
Yes, I saw him too.
That was the PROXY I saw in Romdeau.
The first one that ever terrified me...
But...
I must confirm the effectiveness of FP bullets:
whether they can actually kill a PROXY.
So you're going to shoot him then, Re-l.
Stay calm.
We have only two FP bullets.
Right.
You weren't wrong.
The man we've been after all this time...
is the PROXY.
We can go back to Romdeau now.
Why'd you shoot that one?
Iggy.
Vital signs: negative.
I see. So it's dead.
Miss Re-l...
I saw it with my own eyes.
You are indeed a PROXY.
And this gun is the only weapon capable of killing a PROXY.
Vincent, I can kill you by pulling this trigger.
Kill me?
Did you say that you'd kill me?
Stop it!
Miss... Re-l...
But I won't kill you for now.
I'll go with you.
Re-l...
What I want is the truth!
Not a PROXY's death.
But this bullet...
I'll unleash it on you someday.
Can you still say that you love me?
It's still quite impressive.
I'm sure Daedalus will be happy.
I can't go back to Romdeau by myself.
Tell Daedalus everything you saw here.
No. I can't accept that order.
You should go back to Romdeau as well.
Since that man is a PROXY, it's all the more reason to.
It's too dangerous.
Why?
You wouldn't understand.
"Why"?
If I don't know why myself,
how can you, an autoreiv, know why?
Re-l, I-
Application off.
Obey me, Iggy.
Go back to Romdeau.
Understood.
I will return to Romdeau.
Confirmation requested.
Confirmed.
What's going to happen?
What's going to happen...
from now on?
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
The cogito virus.
The chain of sorrowful hearts that have lost their raison d'être.
When he ceases to be himself,
meditation  conceptual blind spot
a shot rings out in the labyrinthine forest.